(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T17:31:45.125364",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
昔々、あるところにチョコレートの魔法がかかったお城がありました。
Once upon a time, in a certain place, there was a castle under a chocolate spell.
お城の本当の姿はとっても可愛い姿をしているのに、今は魔法のチョコレートのせいで…
Though the castle's true appearance is extremely cute, now because of the magic chocolate...
可愛いどころかほど遠い、ダークな雰囲気のお城です。
far from being cute, it's a castle with a dark atmosphere.
そこに一人の悪魔がやってきました。
Into that place, a single demon came along.
あら、とってもかっこいいお城じゃない？
Oh, isn't this a very cool castle?
ここでは私の歌とダンスをより届けるのも悪くないわね。
It wouldn't be bad to deliver my songs and dances even better from here, right?
そう言うと、悪魔は仲間たちと一緒にクールでセクシーなライブを始めました。
So saying, the demon along with her friends started a cool and sexy live show.
するとどうでしょう。ライブの熱気でまたたく間に、お城のチョコレートが溶けていくではありませんか。
And what do you know? With the heat of the live show, in the blink of an eye, the castle's chocolate began to melt away.
本来の姿を取り戻した、可愛いお城で今度は…あ、うん？
In the cute castle that regained its true form, next... Ah, huh?
んー…番長？
Hmm... Bancho?
もう、せっかく読んであげたのにー！
Geez, even though I went out of my way to read it to you!
ねえ、寝ちゃったの？
Hey, did you fall asleep?
あらあら、寝顔も可愛いわね。
My my, even your sleeping face is cute.
どんな夢見てるのかしら？
I wonder what kind of dream you're seeing?
人ばかりの光 月明かりの代わり
In the crowded light, replacing the moonlight,
見下ろした街並み 少しも惹かれない
The cityscape I look down upon doesn't appeal to me at all.
息つく暇もないほど 気持ち この時間も惜しい
With no time to even catch my breath, even this moment is precious.
焦らすのも嗜好 そういうのでいい？
Teasing is also a preference, is that kind of thing okay?
guilty pleasure 蜜 もっと飲ませて
Guilty pleasure, let me drink more of the nectar,
もっと言わせて「恥ずかしい」
Let me say more, "It's embarrassing."
君はどこにでもいる boy
You're just like any other boy,
なのに胸がヒリつく why？
Yet my heart stings, why?
いけるこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can,
揺れる輪郭 もう湿ってる got cheat
The trembling contours are already damp, got cheat.
これはありふれている lick
This is commonplace, just a lick,
だけど繰り返したい words
But I want to repeat these words.
いけるこまで行かせて
Let me go as far as I can,
甘い誘惑癖になってる got cheat
Sweet temptations have become a habit, got cheat.
oh 君のせいでも僕のせいでも
Oh, whether it's your fault or mine,
oh 何度でも got cheat
Oh, no matter how many times, got cheat.
繰り返したいの 行けるところまで行かせて
I want to keep repeating this, let me go as far as I can.
甘い誘惑 癖になるガッチ
Sweet temptations, a habit-forming Gatch!
君のせいでも 僕のせいでも どちらでもガッチ
Whether it's your fault or my fault, either way, Gatch!
君のせいでも 僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or my fault...
どちらでもガッチ
Either way, Gatch!
確かめてよ合言葉 ただ求めて欲しい
Check the password, just want you to keep asking.
バレルまで間違い よそ見はしないで
Mistakes until it leaks, don't look away.
とげ もっと合わせて もっと先まで
Thorns, match them more, further ahead.
鍵 もっと回して もっと匂わせて
Keys, turn them more, make it smell more.
恋が散りばめている理
The logic scattered by love.
僕を慰めていると 思考やちぎれるまで 行けるところまで行かせて
Comforting me until my thoughts tear apart, let me go as far as I can.
触れる金庫を破るガッチ 君はどこにでもいるのに
Breaking the touched safe, Gatch! Even though you're everywhere,
なのに胸がヒリつくわ 行けるところまで行かせて
Yet my chest tingles, let me go as far as I can.
揺れるリンクも閉めてるガッチ
Closing the swaying link too, Gatch!
これが針触れている理
This is the logic where the needle touches.
だけど繰り返したいの 行けるところまで行かせて
Still, I want to keep repeating this, let me go as far as I can.
甘い誘惑 癖になるガッチ
Sweet temptations, a habit-forming Gatch!
君のせいでも 僕のせいでも
Whether it's your fault or my fault...
なんどもガッチ
No matter how many times, Gatch!
はーい、ということで！ゆづきちょこ生誕祭2025、始始まりましたー！イェーイ！
Hiii, so! Yuzuki Choco's Birthday Festival 2025 has started! Yay!
1曲目はー、ガッチ！Got Cheatをみんな覚えてたー？
The first song was... Gatch! Did everyone remember 'Got Cheat'?
ねえ、どうなったかな？どうだったかなー？
Hey, how did it turn out? How was it?
そして！今回のライブのハッシュタグは、こちらー！#癒月ちょこ生誕祭2025
And! The hashtag for this live is right here! #YuzukiChocoBirthday2025
まあぜひぜひ、ちくしょーとかね、感想を、どんどんXにポストしてくださいー！
Please definitely post your impressions, like #chikusho, on X!
さてさて、冒頭で、バンチョーに読み聞かせしてたちょこなんですけどー、
Now then, at the start, Choco was reading a story to Banchou...
みんな、内容覚えてるー？
Does everyone remember the content?
むかしむかしあるところに、チョコレートの魔法がかかったお城がありました。
Once upon a time, in a certain place, there was a castle under a chocolate spell.
（おや? おや? チョコレートの魔法がかかったお城？）
(Oh? Oh? A castle under a chocolate spell?)
みてみて、このステージ！今回のステージは、チョコレートでコーティングされているお城ですねー！
Look, look at this stage! This time's stage is a castle coated in chocolate!
ね、ピータン感じがして、めちゃめちゃかっこよくないですかー？
Right, it feels so Pithan and super cool, doesn't it?
まあこのあとね、どうなるかはお楽しみにー！
Well, look forward to seeing what happens next!
バンチョーは今も事務所で説教中なのかなー？
Is Banchou still being scolded at the office?
なんて！
Just kidding!
今回はね、このあとね、いーっぱいちょこの仲間たちも呼んでいるので、みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていきましょうー！
This time, after this, we've invited lots of Choco's friends, so let's all get excited together!
それでは、最初のゲストさんは、こちらです！
Now then, our first guest is right here!
次の曲へ、ゴー！
To the next song, go!
人を過度に信じないように
So I won't trust people too much,
愛さないように期待しないように
won't love them, won't expect anything.
かと言って角が立たないように
Yet so I don't cause any friction,
きっとらぬようにめったぬように
keeping out of sight, avoiding trouble.
誰一人傷つけないように
So I won't hurt a single person,
いじめのように殺さぬように
won't bully or kill anyone.
かと言って偽善がバレないように
Yet so my hypocrisy isn't exposed,
威張らないように
so I don't act arrogant.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れないように
And don't forget light jokes or lip service either,
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
smiling through all times and acting charming.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
とかく言わずにだんぽめし上がれ
eat it up without saying a word.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
picky eaters need to fix their habits.
頭空っぽその後に残る心が本物なら
If the heart left behind after an empty mind is real,
きっと君だって同じこと
surely you're the exact same.
「ところで一つ伺いますが 先日何処かで…・やっぱりいいや」
"By the way, I wanted to ask, the other day somewhere... never mind."
無駄に自我を晒さぬように
So I don't needlessly expose my ego,
話さぬように分からぬように
so I don't speak, so I'm not understood.
でも絶対口を閉ざさぬように
Yet so I never close my mouth,
笑わすより笑われるように
so I'm laughed at rather than making others laugh.
人をちゃんと敬うように
So I properly respect people,
崇めるように讃えるように
so I worship and praise them.
でも決して嫌味にならないように
Yet so it never sounds sarcastic,
ふざけないように
so I don't fool around.
集団参加の終身刑 またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
Lifetime sentence of group participation, saying yes again and again—
「あれっ前髪ちょーぜつさいきょうじゃん」とかどうでもいいのにいっちゃって
"Oh your bangs are super ultimate cute!" saying things like that even when it doesn't matter.
前ヤス前は文字通り回収常時社会の集団リンチ
Former yas, former literally reclaimed, regular society's group lynching,
でも決して発狂しないように
but making sure never to go insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
sometimes lonely love stains you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
立つ鳥の後きっとそのあと
the bird leaving leaves its mark behind.
初めはあんな大層な大言壮語を並べたが
At first I lined up such grand boasts,
嫌よ嫌よも好きの内
but reluctance is also a form of affection.
いやいやよも好きのうち
Reluctance is a form of affection,
いやはやしかし曲を初めてでこんな問われ君センスあるよ
but my goodness, starting a song like this, you've got great sense!
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration in the season of love,
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
bitter choco decoration with feelings of love.
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U ビターチョコデコレーション
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U, bitter choco decoration,
皆が望む理想に憧れて
yearning for the ideal everyone desires.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
ボクは心ごとすべて灰にして
I'll turn my whole heart into ash.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
自我を殺して闇に埋めて
killing my ego and burying it in darkness.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration,
ボクは大人になってしまったよママ
I've grown up now, Mom.
明日の一等賞の先も 地獄は続くどこまでも
Even beyond tomorrow's first prize, hell goes on forever.
アナタからどうか今だけは 子どもの頃の気持ちのままで
Please, from you, just for now, keep the feelings of a child.
一緒に絡まずやってこうぜ あの思い出したいんだあのときの気持ち
Let's get through it without tangling together, I want to remember those feelings.
めそめそ泣かないで 笑うより笑われるように
Don't sob and cry, be laughed at rather than laughing.
ビターチョコデコレーション 恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration in the season of love...
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション F.U.C.K.Y.O.U ビターチョコデコレーション
...with feelings of love, F.U.C.K.Y.O.U, bitter choco decoration.
やっぱいいや
Never mind after all.
好きですか の難題に
To the difficult question of "Do you love me?"
笑顔で返すしかない
I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように
As if teased by a demon,
私の答えを君は待っている
you are waiting for my answer.
放課後の教室に
In the after-school classroom,
好きですか の難題に
To the difficult question of "Do you love me?"
笑顔で返すしかない
I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように
As if teased by a demon,
私の答えを君は待っている
you are waiting for my answer.
あわい恋でした ってアルバムに
It would be better to put it in an album
してあげたほうがいい
as a faint love affair.
終わりを告げるチャイムが
I am terribly scared of when
いつ鳴るのか それがたまらなく怖い
the chime signaling the end will ring.
きっとあの子の方が必要似合うよなんて
Surely that girl suits you better,
猿制服と 揺れる白衣
monkey uniform and swaying white coat.
ふとした言葉も傷つけてしまう
Even casual words end up hurting.
失うものがない無邪気な目で苦しめないで
Don't torment me with innocent eyes.
君のテストに大人さえも答えられない
Even adults can't answer your test,
言葉に詰まる
stumbling for words.
「好きだよ」と全部捨てて
Even though I want to throw everything away
抱き寄せてしまいたいのに
and pull you into an embrace saying "I love you".
電気消して 倒れ込む bed
Turn off the lights and fall onto the bed,
息つく暇もなくて 確かめてよ lips
with no time to catch my breath, confirm with lips.
甘い恋で仕立て
Tailored with sweet love,
アルバムにしてあげた方がいい
it's better to put it in an album.
終わんのよ 続く日々が いつなれば
Days that keep going without end—when will they end?
それがたまらなく怖い きっとあの頃の
That's unbearably scary. Surely, compared to those days...
君の方が 見慣れない愛だなんて
Saying you want unfamiliar love—
サボる制服と 揺れる白日
skipping school in uniform under the swaying daylight.
ふとした言葉も 傷つけてしまう
Even a casual word ends up hurting,
失うものが 何もない
and there's nothing left to lose.
無邪気な目で 苦しめないで
Don't torment me with those innocent eyes.
君のテストに 大人さえも答えられない
Not even an adult can answer your test,
言葉に詰まる 好きだよと全部捨てて
and I stumble over my words, wanting to throw everything away and say "I love you,"
抱きしめてしまいたいのに
even though I just want to hold you tight.
そんな強い心じゃ いられない
I can't stay with a heart that strong.
私の答えに バツをつけて
Put a cross on my answer.
そんな強い心じゃ いられない
I can't stay with a heart that strong.
私の答えに バツをつけて
Put a cross on my answer.
これでいい 君のために
Is this fine? For your sake,
そう決めたのに サル制服へ
even though I decided that—heading toward the uniform...
靡く白日 思わず君を引き止める
the fluttering daylight makes me unconsciously stop you.
好きですか？ の難題に
"Do you love me?" To that difficult question,
許されない答えを書いた
I wrote an unpardonable answer.
君の明日を 縛るだけの
Only binding your tomorrow,
ひとりよがりな 恋の約束
a selfish promise of love.
なら君の悲しむ顔も 見送らなくていいなら
If I don't even have to watch your sad face as you leave,
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい
I don't care if I'm called a devil.
甘くトロけるような 一時をあなたに
Just a moment of melting sweetness to you.
僕ら並べては皆ほらライアー
When we line up, everyone, look, we're liars.
理屈だなんてゴミ箱は 身に覚えあるんでしょさあ
Excuses belong in the trash. You remember that, right? Come on.
チクチク痛いので
It stings and hurts,
エゴイズムを奪らされて 縋り割れてくアンサー
having our egoism snatched away, answers clinging and breaking apart.
君は傷つけて悪魔っても
Even if you hurt me and are called a devil,
癒やしてあげるもよ
I'll heal you too.
あ、お目覚めですか？
Ah, are you awake?
さあディンドンディンドン響いてディンドン 笑い合ってはっはっとさけんで
Come on, ding-dong, echoing ding-dong, laughing together, shouting "ha-ha!"
ディンドンディンドン鳴らせよディンドン 闇の先こ 読むのをさしてこ
Ding-dong, make it ring, ding-dong. Read ahead into the darkness.
髪突き足すのには 慰めもなしわ 私の胸で
For adding hair-pulling, there's no comfort—on my chest.
明日だのディスタンス
Tomorrow's distance.
闇に惑え甘いチョコにとろけてく
Wandering in the darkness, melting into sweet chocolate.
錆びた鎖繋がれては解いてく
Tied with rusted chains, untying them.
針貫くが飛ばして瞳を貸してく
Piercing needles, skipping, lending your eyes.
目が覚むように奪らされて
Snatched away so that you wake up,
縋り割れてくアンサー アンサー
answers clinging and breaking apart.
間違えて正しくても 癒やしてあげるもよ
Even if it's wrong or right, I'll heal you.
あ、まだだめですか？
Ah, is it still no good?
ディンドンディンドン狂わせディンドン 最後にハッハッと言って
Ding-dong, driving me crazy, ding-dong, finally shouting "ha-ha!"
ディンドンディンドン迷わずディンドン 覚める前に
Ding-dong, without hesitation, ding-dong, before waking up.
口づけをディンドンディンドン 響いてディンドン 笑い合ってはっはっと叫んで
A kiss—ding-dong, echoing ding-dong, laughing together, shouting "ha-ha!"
デンドンデンドン 鳴らせよデンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ring the ding-dong
闇夜のがおさきか 闇夜のがおさきか
Is the dark night going ahead?
髪付きの日のいを
The scent of days attached to hair
慰さむのしおいは
The tide of solace
私 ものいで
As my own thing
明日たらノディスタンス
Tomorrow is No Distance
静かな午後 淡い日差し
A quiet afternoon, faint sunlight
カーテンが揺れる キミの声
Curtains sway, and it's your voice
近づく足音だけで分かる
I know just by your approaching footsteps
さあ 今日はどんな味が お好み？
Now, what flavor do you prefer today?
囁く悪魔の誘惑 what do you want?
A whispering demon's temptation, what do you want?
sickbayで待ち合わせ mistakeなヨカン
Meeting at the sickbay, a mistaken premonition
扉開けて さあこっちへおいて
Open the door and come over here
教科書に載っていない この気持ちは何ですか？
This feeling not found in any textbook—what is it?
可愛い可愛い顔みせて
Show me your cute, cute face
sickbayで会いましょう mistakeしちゃう？
Let's meet at the sickbay, will we make a mistake?
永遠に続け 時間止まって
Continue forever, time, stand still
教室じゃみせられない 笑顔の秘密は
The secret behind the smile you can't show in class
甘い甘いお菓子あげる 囁く悪魔の誘惑 い・か・が
I'll give you sweet, sweet treats. A whispering demon's temptation—how's that?
秒針のリズム 追い越してくる
Overtaking the rhythm of the second hand
聴かせて もっと キミの心拍
Let me hear more of your heartbeat
触れる視線で 身体中
With touching gazes, throughout my body
騒ぐの もうどうしようもないくらい
It stirs up so much I can't help it
禁断の果実 甘い もう後に戻れない
The forbidden fruit is sweet; there's no turning back now
目が合って はにかんで 触れ合って 見つめ合って
Our eyes meet, we smile shyly, touch and gaze at each other
永遠の楽園に 誘う愛の言葉を
Words of love inviting you to an eternal paradise
耳元で 囁いてあげる
Whispered right into your ear
sickbayで待ってるわ mistakeな時間
Waiting at the sickbay, a mistaken time
扉閉めて もっと近づいて
Close the door and come closer
神様も止められない この気持ちの正体を
The true nature of this feeling that even God can't stop
知らないふりは もう出来ない
I can't pretend not to know anymore
sickbayで会いたいのに mistakeしましょう
Even though I want to meet at the sickbay, let's make a mistake
永遠はここにあるって 信じて
Believe that eternity is right here
キミにしかみせられない 笑顔の裏側
The flip side of the smile I only show you
甘い甘い果実あげる 囁く悪魔の誘惑 もっといかが？
I'll give you sweet, sweet fruit. A whispering demon's temptation—want some more?
いつでもここで待って る my cute student ♡
Always waiting right here for you, my cute student
のーでぃーきりすます！
No-dey Christmas!
おどろおどろしい季節 駆け足ですぎ
A spooky season passes by in a rush
銀白も色変わる 真っ赤なセーメリ季節
Even silver-white changes color to a bright red Christmas season
悪魔にそっと告げて
Whisper softly to the devil
至福の奥に溺れる
Drowning deep in bliss
雪降るツリーに
On the snow-falling tree
欲張りなお願いの山
A mountain of greedy wishes
走って言われると
When told to run
いじわるしせくぬちゃうな
It makes me want to tease you
ちゃんとお願いをして
Make your wish properly
のーでぃーきりすます
No-dey Christmas
悪い子にはご褒美が
Bad children get a reward
サンタより悪魔はいかが 願いをかけてあげる
How about a devil instead of Santa? I'll grant your wish
また何が変わった？ ごひずりさん
What changed again? Gohizuri-san
Welcome to my spooky scary Sickbay
おどろおどろしい季節駆け足で過ぎ
The grim and eerie season passes in a hurry,
純白も色を変える
even pure white changes its color.
真っ赤な聖なる季節悪夢に衝突して
The bright red holy season collides with a nightmare,
漆黒の雲に覆われる
covered by pitch-black clouds.
雪降るツリーによくばりなお願いの山
A mountain of greedy wishes on the snowy tree.
ほしいって言われると
When you say you want it,
いじわるしたくなっちゃうな
I can't help wanting to tease you.
「ちゃんとお願いして？」
"Can you beg for it properly?"
のーばでぃーくりすます！
Nobody's Christmas!
悪い子にはご褒美なし
No reward for bad children,
サンタより悪魔はいかが？
how about a devil instead of Santa?
願いを叶えてあげる
I'll grant your wish,
また罠にかかった子羊さん
another little lamb caught in a trap.
welcome to my spooky scary sickbay
聖夜もゴーストパーティーももう私のもの
Both the holy night and the ghost party are mine.
もちろんそこの隙間ないキミも
Of course, that slippery fool there too.
あれもこれもって
This and that...
目移りして困ってない？
Aren't your eyes wandering?
そんなほしいものリスト
That kind of wishlist
消しておきました
I've already erased.
「欲望さらけだして」
"Expose your desires."
のーばでぃーくりすます！
Nobody's Christmas!
ツリーの下にびっくり箱
A surprise box under the tree,
驚いた表情はケーキよりデリシャスです
your surprised expression is tastier than cake.
もっと見せてその表情
Show me that expression even more!
良い子なふりしてるだけでしょう？
You're just pretending to be a good kid, right?
昼夜逆転しちゃってるんでしょう？
Your day and night are reversed, aren't they?
プレゼントもういらないんでしょう？
You don't need presents anymore, do you?
だって私だけいれば満足でしょう？
Because you'd be satisfied with just me, right?
その靴下の中に
Inside that stocking,
甘い誘惑をin
I put a sweet temptation in.
諦めておいて
Just give up and accept it—
ah christmas for nobody
のーばでぃーくりすます！
Nobody's Christmas!
悪い子が夜更かししてる
Bad kids staying up late,
クソガキにunholy night
an unholy night for brats.
甘い甘いお仕置きです
A sweet, sweet punishment!
聖夜の前だけいい子のふりして
Pretending to be good right before the holy night,
飴もらおうって企みなんて
scheming to get some candy...
甘いんですほらほらよろこんで！
how naive! Come on, rejoice!
恐怖と惑わげちゃうね
I'll fill you with terror and bewilderment!
のーばでぃーくりすます！
Nobody's Christmas!
Watch Me
[Title: Watch Me]
巡り合う糸はきっと
The threads that cross paths
絡まるようになってる
are bound to tangle together.
リアルで感じる熱は
The warmth felt in reality
本物の誘惑
is a genuine temptation.
時々高鳴る鼓動は焦り速度が追いつけない
My beating heart races too fast to catch up.
期待の先に映る
Reflected beyond my expectations,
キミがいて 目に見えないメロディが
you are there, and an invisible melody
弾ける気がしたの
feels like it's about to burst.
ときめきは いつまでも変わらない夢の証でしょう
This excitement is proof of an unchanging dream.
願いごと集めてく カラフルに彩る通り それじゃパシャっと
Gathering wishes along a colorful street, now snap!
決めポーズ リズムに合わせてダンスダンス 踊ろうよ 踏み出して
Strike a pose, dance to the rhythm! Come on, take a step forward.
全身のハートで見せつけていく これでもおそと おなじ
Show it off with all your heart, even outside it's the same.
最後はぎゅっと 決めポーズ リズムに合わせてダンスダンス 踊ろうよ 駆け抜けて
Finish with a tight pose, dance to the rhythm! Run all the way through.
天使の微笑み ドキドキさせて これでもおそと 同じだね
Make my heart race with an angel's smile, even outside it's the same.
だらだらしてたら お昼まで進めず
Lazing around gets us nowhere by noon.
腹ぺこへっこ取る おなかからグー
A hungry stomach growls, "Goo!"
あつまってカフェで決めた 暗号は 最後であげた
The secret code decided at the café was given at the end.
まったり編たり案外のんびり悪くないね 迷走中
Relaxing and knitting isn't half bad while wandering.
時々高鳴る鼓動は心拍数まだ追いつけない
My racing heart still can't keep up with the pulse.
直流に微笑む キミがいて
You smile right before my eyes,
風邪気味で届いた日の 魔法みたいにずっと
like magic on that day I caught a cold.
友達は いつまでも 忘れない 想いを広げて
Spreading feelings we'll never forget as friends,
どこまでも 続いてく 同じ未来を見つめたい
I want to look toward the same future stretching on forever.
ゃらりぱっぱりぱっぱりらっぱ
Lali-pa-pala-pa-pa-pala-pa,
私の心の距離
the distance between our hearts
おつなぐいと
connected by a single thread.
準備はOK？
Are you ready?
それじゃぱんぱん！
Here we go!
早速ポーズを教せてだった
Let's strike a quick pose,
踊ろうよ輝いて
and dance while shining bright!
天使の言葉でとりこにしてく
Captivating you with angelic words,
これでもおそなじ
even then, we're the same.
最後はギュッと締めポーズ 心に訪ねてだった
Finally, a tight closing pose, asking in our hearts,
踊ろうよ飛び込んで
let's dance and dive right in,
天使の微笑みドキドキさせて
making hearts race with an angel's smile!
これでもおそなじだね
Even then, we're the same.
(sweetest love)
聞いて 会いたいのに 飛んできて
Listen, I want to see you, fly over here!
すここまるくらいに おねだり
Begging you just enough to trouble you.
ねぇちょっと聞いて見て受け取って
Hey, listen, look, and take it in,
甘くとめまいしちゃうような時を
a time so sweet it makes me dizzy.
疲れ顔して いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You look tired, always working so hard,
もう全部流して 全部食べてあげようか
should I wash it all away and eat it all up for you?
よそ見なんて嫌だよ ちゃんとこっち向いていなっちょ
Looking away is no good, look right here at me!
目と目が合うでしょ 痺れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Our eyes meet, right? Look at me till you're numb!
ひとつ 夢中にさせて ふたつ 見つけてね
One, get lost in a dream. Two, find me.
もういっか とりこにしちゃうな 心拍数急上昇
Whatever, let's get captivated, heart rate skyrocketing!
好きよ
I love you!
いたいのはい の飛んできて
I want to see you, fly over here,
不安な顔より笑顔みせて
show a smile instead of worry!
ねぇちょっと聞いて見て受け取って
Hey, listen, look, and take it in,
甘いチョコのような時を
a time like sweet chocolate!
ここにいたいのに いつのまに欲張っちゃう
I want to stay here, but before I know it, I get greedy,
冬の日にちょっとひとくち 散らしちゃうわよ 食べもちょっと
taking a little bite on a winter day and scattering it around!
不安なんて抱えて らしくないのなんて思ってた
Carrying worries and thinking "that's not like me,"
全部全部まるごと 包み込んで溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap it all up and melt it away for you.
どうして 何してても 気持ちは同じなんだね
No matter what we do, our feelings are the same.
ここだって どこだって 想いは伝わるから
Right here, anywhere, our thoughts get through.
声にして 文字にして 勇気出して好きって伝えて
Put it in voice, put it in words, find the courage to say "I love you."
今日だって いつだって 愛し返すの
Today and always, returning your love!
(sweetest love)
隠さないでちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me properly!
キミのこと全部を
Everything about you—
ちょーだい
give it to me!
聞いて 会いたいのに 飛んできて
Listen, I want to see you, fly over here!
少し困るくらいにお願い
Begging you just enough to trouble you.
あした起きたら
If I wake up tomorrow,
夢だと思うかな
I wonder if it'll feel like a dream.
いっぱいの光と音
Filled with light and sound,
私を連れ出して
lead me away.
ユーフォリア
Euphoria
ふたり世界は
Our world is
甘くて優しくて 恋い焦がれた
sweet, gentle, and deeply yearned for.
そんな感情 初めてで 出会えたんだよ
It's my first time feeling this way—I'm so glad I met you.
ねえ 聞かせてみて
Hey, let me hear it—
その歌で合図して 叩いて
give me a sign with your song and beat the rhythm.
うん 濃厚だよ
Yeah, it's so rich and deep.
これからもよろしくね
Please take care of me from now on too.
隣歩いて行きたいな
I want to walk side by side with you.
あふれそうな想いが こんなにも胸をしめつけるんだとして
If these overflowing feelings tighten my chest so much,
なぜうまく言葉にできないよ
why can't I put it into words well?
あなたを想うよりも
More than just thinking of you,
私をしあわせだよ
it makes me so happy.
この手の温もりが 大切で愛しい
The warmth of this hand is precious and dear—
マイ ユーフォリア
my euphoria.
ふたり世界は
Our world is
色づくきらめいて 焦らないな
colorful, sparkling, and unhurried.
まだまだ知らないが 楽しんだ
There's still so much we don't know, let's enjoy it.
ねえ 紡いでみよう
Hey, let's spin it together—
続きの話を もう一度って
asking to hear the continuation once more.
うん ありがとうだよ
Yeah, thank you so much.
お待たせ そのその先で
Sorry to keep you waiting, and beyond that,
あなた笑っていてくれて 嬉しいの
I'm so glad to see you smiling.
ズルイよ
It's unfair...
the future with you, I will be smiling
お互い笑顔でいよ
Let's both keep smiling.
終わりの日も変わらずに
Even on our final day, unchanging,
これからのことを思うたび
every time I think of the future ahead,
少しだけ泣いちゃうような
I feel like crying a little bit—
あれ この気持ちどう伝えがせないよ
ah, how can I convey this feeling?
あなたといられるから
Because I get to be with you,
私をしあわせだよ
it makes me so happy.
一瞬の足音が 特別で愛しい
The sound of our footsteps in this fleeting moment is special and dear—
マイ ユーフォリア
my euphoria.
はーい、ということで、ここまでいかがだったでしょうかー！
Ha~i! So, how was it up to this point?!
たくさんチョコのお友達たちが来てくれました！ありがとうー！
Lots of Choco's friends came to see us! Thank you so much!
まあね、いよいよライブも終盤ですが、最後まで楽しんでいってくださいくださーい！
Well, we're finally reaching the climax of the live show, so please enjoy it all the way to the end!
そしてそして、このステージどうですかー？
And, and... how do you like this stage?
まあ最初はチョコでコーディングされたシックでかっこいいお城だったんですけどー
Well, at first it was a chic and cool castle themed around Choco...
みんなと踊って、その熱と手々でチョコが暑苦しくて取れちゃいました！
But after dancing with everyone, with all that passion and warmth, Choco got so hot she took it off!
見てよみんな！もうね、ビターチョコから
Look at everyone! From being bitter Choco...
ツイートでキュートなホワイトチョコに
To the cute white chocolate on Twitter,
ピンチが早変わり
the pinch quickly changes!
まあ、みんなはどっちの方が好みだったかは
Well, which one did everyone prefer?
まあ、あとの感想でぜひぜひ 教えてください
Please be sure to let me know in your feedback later!
まあね、ま、この続きはちょっとまだゲストパートなんですけど、まあね
Well, this continuation is still the guest part, but...
最後 誰がどうなっちゃうのかな
In the end, who will turn out how?
まあちょっと予想してみてください
Well, try to guess!
はーい！
Yes!
それでは 最後ね
Well then, finally...
ま、最後って言っても全体では最後じゃないけど、ゲストパートは最後なんだ
Well, even if I say finally, it's not the overall end, but the guest part is the end.
みんなちゃんと楽しんでる？いけてますか？
Is everyone enjoying it properly? Are you doing well?
本当いつもお祝いしてくれてありがとう。じゃあ、最後のゲストパート曲も
Thank you as always for celebrating. Well then, for the final guest part song...
盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's get hyped!
それでは聞いてください。どうぞ！
Now then, please listen. Here we go!
さあさ この指に止まれ
Come on, catch this finger.
後悔あとでしても知らないぞ
You'll regret it later if you don't know!
音に呑まれて、歌って踊って満たすだけ
Swallowed by the sound, just singing, dancing, and fulfilling it.
パンパン 手を打ち鳴らして
Clap, clap, clapping your hands,
ソソソラシド ん な五線譜も
even on such a so-so-sol-la-ti-do staff,
音色を敷いて、今 導き出すよ
laying out the tone, I'll guide it out now.
正体は 実は 案外 歯がゆいもの
The true identity is actually surprisingly frustrating.
魔法のタクト、空にかざすだけ
Just holding the magic baton up to the sky.
おいでよ 街を包み込んだ 超常現象が
Come on, the paranormal phenomenon wrapping around the town
夜空に、ほら こだまして 退屈が泣き出す
echoes in the night sky, making boredom start to cry.
孤独な 愛を埋めよう 最終 妄想的 のクターンが
Let's fill the lonely love. The final illusory nocturne...
君は 聞こえた？ 星に舞う旋律を
Did you hear it? The melody dancing in the stars.
ワンツーさんしで 泣いていた
Crying with one, two, three, four,
過去に負けない めぐる力の
turning the power that won't lose to the past,
た・た・楽しいリズムで 途切れ無い音を乗せてたったん
carrying unbroken notes with a fun, fun rhythm.
痛い愛を描こう セプテット
Let's draw painful love, Septet.
忘れてた 景色 の向こうの その向こう
Forgotten scenery, beyond and beyond.
未達 調和のほころび
Unreached harmony's fray,
モノクロの望遠鏡
monochrome telescope.
待った私の ぶっつけ本番で 奏でよう
Wait, let's play it in my impromptu performance.
理想 輝く 幻想的 思考で いつも目が合うあいつと
With ideal, glowing, fantastical thoughts, with that guy whose eyes always meet mine,
手を繋ぎ踊ろう 何度も泣いて泣いた 心のエレジーを
let's hold hands and dance, the elegy of a heart that cried and cried so many times.
僕は聴こえた だから今ここにいるんだ
I heard it, that's why I'm here now.
招待は 実は 案外 悲しいもの
The invitation is actually surprisingly sad.
魔法の音色、空に響かせて
Let the magic tone resonate through the sky.
おいでよ 街を包み込んだ 超常現象が
Come on, the paranormal phenomenon wrapping around the town
夜空に、ほら こだまして 退屈が泣き出す
echoes in the night sky, making boredom start to cry.
愉快な 歌を歌おう 最終
Let's sing a cheerful song, the final...
アンサンブルを
The ensemble...
君は聞こえた
Did you hear it?
星にまう旋律を
The melody dancing among the stars
ワンツースリーシで泣いてた
Crying on one, two, three, four...
過去に負けない巡る力を
The power to not lose to the past
タンタン楽しいリズムで途切れない音をのせてた
Riding a joyful, uninterrupted rhythm
パンパン手打ち鳴らして 踊れ踊れ 大怪獣トラ！
Clap your hands and dance, dance, giant monster tiger!
バイバイ今夜はさよなら 次は君もステージで タタン！
Bye-bye tonight, next time you're on stage too!
さあさあこの指にとまれ 後悔あとでしても知らないぞ
Take my hand, you'll regret it if you miss out!
耳をすまして 僕らと踊るだけ
Listen closely, just dancing along with us
はーい！ちょくまろ全員集合！うわー！イエーイ！
Hii! Chokumaro, everyone gather! Woah! Yay!
イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
いや今日のちょくちょく食べてくれてありがとう！
Thanks so much for eating Choco-stuff today!
いや、こちらこそ！ありがとうございます！
No, thank you! Thank you very much!
え、ちょこせん誕生日おめでとう！おめでとう！わーい！
Um, Choco-sen, happy birthday! Happy birthday! Yay!
ケーキ食べた？食べた！食べた！おめでとうございます！
Did you eat cake? I did! I did! Happy birthday!
いや、もし幸せだわちょこ、ちょっとケーキ持ってくればよかった、忘れちゃったわ！
Man, I'm so happy, Choco. I should've brought some cake, I forgot!
忘れてた！いや、まあまあ、今日はね
I forgot! Well, anyway, today...
じゃあちょっとちょこの誕生日プレゼントにちょっとちょこに付き合ってもらってもいいですか？
Um, for Choco's birthday present, would you keep Choco company?
いいよ、もちろん！
Sure, of course!
ちょっとちょこみんなとやりたいことがあって
Choco has something she wants to do with everyone...
え、何？何？なんだろ？
Eh, what? What? What is it?
あのー、ちーと一一緒にグッズ告知してほしいな、世界！
Um, I want everyone to help announce the goods together!
一緒に？いいでしょ？
Together? Sounds good, right?
いいでしょ、ちょっとなんかピキッとした、今。いいでしょ。
Sounds good, you look a bit tense right now. Sounds good.
なんだっけ、ポールダンスとかかと思った。ポールダンスもやりたい！ポールダンスやりたい！
I thought it was pole dancing. I wanna do pole dancing!
ひまちゃんの見たい！ちょこ、ちょこのチャンネル危ないぞ、これ！
I wanna see Hima-chan's! Choco, your channel's in danger!
やばい！やばい！ということで、では今回も夜ちょこ誕生日記念グッズが出ます！
Oh no! With that said, Yuzuki Choco birthday goods are out!
出ます！出ます！出ます！
They're out! They're out! They're out!
それでは1つずつ見ていきましょう。まず1つ目は
Let's check them out one by one. First up is...
こちら！ワイドラバーマット！
This! Wide rubber mat!
はい、こちらのね、イラストはNardack先生が描いていただきました！
Yes, this illustration was drawn by Nardack-sensei!
かわいいね！
It's so cute!
いや、Nardack、Nardack先生、大好きです！かっこいい！かわいいね！
Man, Nardack-sensei, I love you! So cool! So cute!
ちょっと毎年ちょこの誕生日はね、Nardack先生に描いていただいてて
Every year for Choco's birthday, Nardack-sensei draws it...
いや、去年のもよかったし、よかったね。
Last year's was great too, it was so good.
今年のはめちゃくちゃかっこいい！
This year's is insanely cool!
いや、そうなんですよ。今回はね、かわいいちょことかっこいいちょこの2人がね、ちょっと背中合わせになってるイラストなんですけど。
Yeah. This time, cute Choco and cool Choco are back-to-back.
両方楽しめるやつだ！買います、買いますそうですね！
You can enjoy both! I'm buying it, totally!
ホワイトちょことダークちょこ、両方愛してください！
Please love both White Choco and Dark Choco!
え、食べ、食べていいですか？ずっと？えーと？えーと？
Can I eat it? The whole time? Um? Um?
はい、そしてそして、次のグッズが！
Yes, and then, the next goods!
はい、ちょこめいと法被です！
Yes, it's the Chocomate happi coat!
えーすごい！いいの？
Wow, amazing! Is this okay?
めちゃくちゃ背中の文字が「ちょこめいと」って書いてあって
The writing on the back says 'Chocomate'...
表にはね、ちょっと結城ちょことかいう、この刺繍がまたね、かっこよくていい感じに！
And on the front, this embroidery of Yuzuki Choco is cool!
すごい！刺繍なんだ！そう、推しグッズとしてぜひ。
Wow, it's embroidery! Yeah, definitely as oshi goods.
すごいね、これ直筆サインが縫ったの、これ？
That's amazing, did she sew her own signature?
ちょっとちょこはちょっとあの、裁縫できないんで、あの、そこは、やばい！やばい！
Choco can't sew, so um, as for that—oh no!
まああるけどね、直筆、直筆縫製みたいな。最高！
Well, it's like a handwritten, handwritten sewing. Awesome!
直筆縫製、刺繍はハードル高すぎるの！
Handwritten sewing? Embroidery has too high a hurdle!
一体いくら上がるんだ、それ。5万くらいにするしかない。確かにな、確かに！
How much would that cost? We'd have to make it 50k yen. True!
はい、ちょこの角カチューシャでございます！
Yes, it's Choco's horn headband!
欲しい！欲しい！欲しかったよね！
I want it! I want it! You wanted it, right?
かわいい！
Cute!
いや、そうなんです。これ、全部スパンコールになってて、ギラギラなの！
Yeah. This is all covered in sequins, it's super sparkly!
すごい！つけてるだけでちょこの角の存在感がかわいくてね、つけれちゃう。
Amazing! Just wearing it makes Choco's horns so cute.
誰でも、誰でもちょこになれる！欲しい！欲しい！
Anyone can become Choco! I want it! I want it!
そう、誰でもちょこになれちゃう角カチューシャでございます！ちょこ丸ね、ちょこ丸でちょこになりますように！
It's a horn headband where anyone can become Choco! Chokomaru, may you become Choco!
4人ちょこになりますように！4ちょこに！
May all 4 of us become Choco! 4 Chocos!
これでちょこまろやろう。
Let's do Chocomaro with this.
え、めっっちゃいい、ことかわいい。
Ah, this is amazing, it's so cute!
そしてそして、今年もございます！
And this year as well, we have...
描き下ろし台本の耳なめASMRでございます！
Choco's newly-drawn script ear-licking ASMR!
え、なめちゃ、いいの？ほんとに。
Eh, licking... is that really okay?
え、江戸？ってこと？
Eh, Edo? What does that mean?
え、江戸。え、わかしてくださいよ。
Eh, Edo. Please explain it to me.
なめ？江戸だよ。
Lick? It's Edo.
え、な、なに？なめ？
Eh, w-what? Lick?
ちょっと、ひまちゃん、ちょっと早いか。耳なめ早いかも。
Wait, Hima-chan, is it too early? Ear-licking might be too early.
え、びっくりした、今。耳をなめ、なめる？
Eh, I was so surprised just now. Licking ears?
そうです！耳をじゅるじゅるしちゃう耳なめASMRでございます！
That's right! It's ear-licking ASMR where I slurp on your ears!
いいんですか？まだ許されてるのおかしいだろ。
Is that okay? It's weird that you're still allowed to do this.
いやいや、いいだろ、これは！奈良ってことか？
No no, it's fine, isn't it! Does that mean Nara?
ちょこ先生！そうですよ！
Choco-sensei! That's right!
ちょっと買いますわ。
I'll buy it right now.
なんで？なんで引き切れてんの、ねにちゃん。
Why? Why are you pulling away, Neni-chan?
お願いします、ちょっと。お願いします、何？
Please, just a little. Please, what?
はい、そしてね、今回フルセットもございます！
And also, this time we have a full set available!
おー！
Oh!
今回はね、フルセット購入特典として、ポストカード、ちょこの直筆サイン入りのね、ものが届きます。
As a full-set purchase bonus, you'll receive a postcard with Choco's handwritten autograph.
そしてそして！さらに、フルセット購入特典がもう一つあります！
And furthermore! There's another full-set purchase bonus!
hololive PRODUCTION OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードがもう一枚ついてきます！
Another card for the hololive PRODUCTION OFFICIAL CARD GAME is included!
え、何それ！すごい！何それ！
Eh, what is that! Amazing! What is that!
特典につくのは、推しアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです！
The bonus is a key card that lets you show off your Oshi—an Oshi Holomen Card!
ええー！なにそれ！すごい！カードゲーム？
Ehh! What is that! Amazing! A card game?
そうなんです、カードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご容赦ください。
That's right, please note that the cards are in Japanese only.
えー、いいな！あります、あります！
Ehh, how nice! There are, there are!
そしてね、ちょこ描き下ろし台本の特別ボイスもついてきます！さらにツイッター、さらに耳も、なめボイスがまた？
And special voice dramas with scripts newly drawn by Choco are included! Furthermore, another ear-licking voice?
え、そんな！次は何なめてもらえるんですか？
Eh, really! What will get licked next?
ぜひ、ぜひ！なめなめされたい方！
By all means! For those who want to be licked!
良くないだろ！最高だよ！最高だろが！最高だ！
That's no good! It's the best! It's the best! It's the best!
そしてここまで告知ぜった！誕生日記念グッズは配信終了後より販売開始となりますので、ぜひぜひ概要欄にあるURLとXの方をチェックしてみてください！
And that's all for the announcements! Birthday goods go on sale right after the stream, so check the URL and X in the description!
お願いします！買いまーす！
Please! I'll buy it!
はい、みんな、もね、でもね、ちょこね、今年一番嬉しかったのは、やっぱこうやってみんながちょこーの配信に来てくれたことが嬉しかったから、ほんとありがとう！
Yeah, everyone! What made me happiest this year is that everyone came to my streams, so thank you so much!
いやいやいや、こちらこそ！嬉しいです！こちらこそ一緒にダンスできて楽しかったです！
No no, same here! We're so glad we could dance together and have fun!
今年もちょこまろやりたい！やりたい！やりたい！
I want to do Chocomaro this year too! I want to! I want to!
今年も一緒に楽しみましょう！はい、ありがとうございます！
Let's enjoy it together this year too! Yes, thank you very much!
それでは、次が最後の曲です！聞いてください！
Well then, the next one is our final song! Please listen!
ふわ～ いい天気、
Puff~ Good weather,
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい
I want to take a nap on the infirmary bed
ズル休み許されない
Playing hooky isn't allowed,
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってる？ちょっとだけ
Slacking off? Just a little.
誰も来ないとやる気でない！
If nobody comes, I've got no motivation!
ちょこちょこせーせーしょん、Yeah!
Choco Choco Sensation, Yeah!
ちょこちょこせーせーしょん、このままだと私 ダメみたい？
Choco Choco Sensation, am I no good just like this?
あー 起きなきゃ うとうと ごろーん
Ah, gotta wake up, dozing off, rolling over
2回目のあくび おやすみなさい
Second yawn, good night
ごめんなさい 少しだけ寝かせて
Sorry, let me sleep just a little longer
先生モード シャットダウン
Teacher mode, shut down
夢見る ふわふわ
Dreaming, fluffy
ずっと こうして眠りたいー
I want to keep sleeping like this
ありがとう ぽかぽか
Thank you, warm and cozy
ちょっと休憩してるだけ
Just taking a little break
油断大敵ね 急に君が来るなんて
Careless enemy! You're coming so suddenly.
ねえ どこか悪いの？ 何かを期待しているのかな？
Hey, is something wrong? Are you expecting something?
ゆらぐ 心 めぐる 感情
Swaying heart, revolving emotions,
くちびるだけ 甘い sensation
Only my lips, a sweet sensation.
癒されたい 甘えていたい
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled.
頼ってよ choco sensation
Depend on me, choco sensation.
君の視線 君の体温
Your gaze, your body temperature.
分かってても 恋は測れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured.
元気なのに ため息ついちゃう
Even though I'm fine, I let out a sigh.
もしかして もう手遅れ？
Could it be... it's already too late?
でも ドキドキ するまで動けないから
But my heart beats so fast I can't move,
トキメキ運んできて my student
Bring me some excitement, my student.
君の視点 君の体温
Your perspective, your body temperature,
分かってても 恋は測れない
Even if I know, love can't be measured.
元気なのに ため息ついちゃう
Even though I'm fine, I let out a sigh.
もしかして もう手遅れ？
Could it be... it's already too late?
でも ドキドキ するまで動けないから
But my heart beats so fast I can't move,
トキメキ運んできて my student
Bring me some excitement, my student.
ズル休み また来たの？
Playing hooky, you came again?
保健室は神聖なの
The infirmary is sacred.
サボってた？ ちょっとだけ
Slacking off? Just a little.
やっぱり君にいてほしい！
As it turns out, I want you to stay!
ちょこちょこせーせーしょん、Yeah!
Choco Choco Sensation, Yeah!
ふぁ～ いい天気、
Phew, such great weather!
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したーい。
Napping on the nurse's office bed.
ズル休み 許されない
Slacking off is not allowed!
保健室は神聖なのごとに
The nurse's office is sacred, you know.
サボってる？ ちょっとだけ
Slacking off? Just a little bit.
誰も来なけりゃ やる気でなーい！
Nobody's coming, I don't feel like it!
choco x2 sensation yay！
Choco x2 sensation, yay!
choco x2 sensation
このままだと 私 ダメ みたい？
Is this how I turn into a hopeless me?
あー 起きなきゃ うと う と ごろーん
Ah, gotta wake up... Dozing off...
2回目のあくび おやすみなさい
The second snooze, good morning.
ごめんなさい 少し だけ 寝かせて
Sorry, let me sleep just a bit longer.
先生 モード シャットダウン
Teacher mode: shut down.
夢見る ふわふわ
Dreaming softly,
ずっと こうして 眠り たいー
I want to keep sleeping like this.
ありがとう ぽかぽか
Thank you, feeling so warm.
ちょっと 休憩 してる だけ
Just taking a short rest.
油断大敵 ね 急 に 君 が 来る なんて
Careful now, you suddenly show up.
ねえ どこ か 悪い の ？
Hey, what's wrong?
何 か を 期待 し て いる の か な ？
Are you expecting something from me?
揺らぐ 心 めぐる 感情
A wavering heart, swirling emotions,
くち づけ 甘い sensation
A bit too sweet sensation.
癒 されたい 甘えて いたいい
I want to be healed, want to be spoiled,
頼っ て よ choco sensation
Lean on me, Choco sensation.
君 の 視線 君 の 体温
Your gaze, your body temperature—
分かっ て も 恋 は 測れ ない
Even so, love cannot be measured.
元気 なのに ため息 つい ちゃう
Feeling energetic yet letting out a sigh,
もしかして 何 か の 病 ？
Could this be some kind of illness?
でも ドキドキ する まで 動け ない から
I can't move until my heart races,
トキメキ 運ん で き て my student
Make my heart flutter, my student!
魔界 だって この 世界 だって
Even in the demon world, even in this world,
みんな 癒し が 必要 だ から
Everyone needs some healing,
だから！
That's why!
ちょこちょこ sensation yay！
Choco-choco sensation, yay!
絶対 君 も ダメ に し たい！
I definitely want to make you useless too!
巡る 心 めぐる 感情
A spinning heart, a swirling feeling,
くちどけ 甘い sensation
A bit too sweet sensation.
癒されたい 甘えていたいよ
I want to be healed, want to be spoiled,
頼ってよ Choco sensation
Rely on me, Choco sensation.
君の視線 君の匂い
Your posture, your scent—
分かっても恋は計れない
Even if I understand, love cannot be measured.
元気なのにため息しちゃうの
Even when I'm energetic, I let out a sigh,
もしかしてもしかしても遅れて
Could it be that this is love sickness?
でもドキドキするまで動けないから
I can't move until my heart races,
ときめき運んできて My student
Make my heart flutter, my student!
ちょこちょこ sensation yay！
Choco-choco sensation, yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい！
I definitely want to make you useless too!